Your challenge for this section is to take a look at SailorView.
I've intentionally left a lot of the styling in there very generic.
In fact, there's a lot of duplication.
You can try actually seeing if you can refactor it in a way that makes more sense to you.
Maybe you want to do it in a global file,
who knows and then you can play one with V-Bind.
Hopefully, people had a chance to play around with some styles.
Like I said, honestly, CSS has its own skill set.
There are plenty of great workshops here on Front-of-Master,
so be sure to check those out if you want to learn more about CSS architecture.
But I hope that was useful in terms of a way to learn what techniques are available to you
out of the gate when it comes to using View,
so that you can use that to augment best practices with CSS.
Because to be very clear, again, as someone who loves CSS,
I'm not advocating for you to work around the Cascade.
The Cascade is extremely powerful.
But like a lot of things, you got to know when to use it in the right scenarios.
And sometimes when it comes to certain components,
it makes sense to just keep it scoped to ignore the Cascade.
And so know that View provides you those options.
And also, as we saw with the V-Bind as well,
when it comes to customization and being able to easily connect your JavaScript with your CSS,
like View tries to do its best to make that as easy as possible for you
when it comes to using compiler-based optimizations.
So I'll just go ahead and just, once again,
let's demo some of that inside of Say Love View
so that you can have that as a solution branch.
And then we will go from there.
So switching on over, CD Say Love View.
Great.
Perfect.
All right.
So first thing first, when I think of Say Love View, as we can see here,
the user card actually is something that sticks out to me
as something that we honestly are not going to share these styles at this moment.
And so when I look at this, honestly, I do think this is probably a good case
for just having the wrapper or these particular styles be scoped to this particular component.
So we can go ahead and scope it like this.
And then, however, though, if you're thinking about it and you're like,
well, there are a lot of other cards out there.
So what if I want to be really specific about this card?
Then you know what, on second thought, let's just make this a CSS module.
Since, again, the styles here are fairly innocuous,
not a lot of reusability at the moment.
So we can just do style.
And then because it's the dash, though, this is where, unfortunately,
the style syntax is a little bit on the uglier side comparatively.
We can see now that it still works because we look at here.
We can see there is our user card that's actually being rendered out as anticipated.
OK, what about other opportunities for style refactoring?
Well, if we take a look at the home page, we have a bunch of stuff here
that's actually fairly generic.
We have stuff in the login page that's being refactored.
So what we could do, really, is we can just actually delete this stuff on the login page.
And then if we refresh and take a look, home, login, everything still looks good.
So that refactor was pretty easy.
And then finally, let's find an opportunity for some scope styles.
Well, if we're looking at the user page, actually, it looks like we're using
a lot of stuff here as well.
So let's go ahead and just wipe this out to finish the refactor.
And if we take a look at home page, we do have that button green right here.
So OK, that's good.
In this case, to be honest, I'm not sure I'd want to scope the styles at this point
because we're inside of home page.
And home page we know is being shared across multiple files.
So at this point, what I would probably do is I'd say, you know what?
Home page styles are not just being shared for its own.
It's being shared across the entire app.
So let's actually just drop that inside of here.
So at the bare minimum, it feels a little bit more proper in terms of cascade.
App.view controls these things are being shared everywhere.
So boom, it's now being shared.
And there are certainly opportunities here to refactor things like, for example,
we're seeing the navigation here.
So you can imagine as this application grows, you can totally see an opportunity
for us to actually refactor our header component into its own file,
which then that might be a good use case for scope, for example.
Anyhow, just want to talk to you some high-level refactoring,
and that's how I might approach it.